[
    {
        "categoria": "Five people are talkin about their work. Listen to the extracts. Write down any of the new words from exercise 9 that include the words in capitals.",
        "pregunta": "(-phone)",
        "respuesta": "cellphone",
        "incorrecta1": "computer",
        "incorrecta2": "laptop",
        "incorrecta3": "microwave",
        "incorrecta4": "tablet",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Complete the sentences",
        "pregunta": "(up-)",
        "respuesta": "upgrade",
        "incorrecta1": "grade",
        "incorrecta2": "up",
        "incorrecta3": "upgrate",
        "incorrecta4": "upgrated",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Complete the sentences",
        "pregunta": "(-cast)",
        "respuesta": "broadcasters",
        "incorrecta1": "broad",
        "incorrecta2": "broatcaster",
        "incorrecta3": "cellphone",
        "incorrecta4": "computer",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Complete the sentences",
        "pregunta": "(down-)",
        "respuesta": "ownload",
        "incorrecta1": "upload",
        "incorrecta2": "townload",
        "incorrecta3": "downloaded",
        "incorrecta4": "loaded",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Complete the sentences",
        "pregunta": "(-ware)",
        "respuesta": "software",
        "incorrecta1": "hardware",
        "incorrecta2": "sofware",
        "incorrecta3": "officeware",
        "incorrecta4": "windoware",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Complete the sentences",
        "pregunta": "(tele-)",
        "respuesta": "telecoms",
        "incorrecta1": "televisa",
        "incorrecta2": "nextel",
        "incorrecta3": "telemit",
        "incorrecta4": "telewindows",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Complete the sentences",
        "pregunta": "(up-)",
        "respuesta": "update",
        "incorrecta1": "date",
        "incorrecta2": "ubdate",
        "incorrecta3": "upoload",
        "incorrecta4": "download",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Complete the sentences",
        "pregunta": "(-byte)",
        "respuesta": "gigabyte",
        "incorrecta1": "terabite",
        "incorrecta2": "tigabyte",
        "incorrecta3": "bites",
        "incorrecta4": "migabite",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    }, 

    {
        "categoria": "Complete the sentences",
        "pregunta": "(tele-)",
        "respuesta": "telecoms/teleconferencing",
        "incorrecta1": "telecomes",
        "incorrecta2": "teleconferencing",
        "incorrecta3": "teleconfered",
        "incorrecta4": "telewifi",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Complete the sentences",
        "pregunta": "(-band)",
        "respuesta": "broadband",
        "incorrecta1": "band",
        "incorrecta2": "wifiband",
        "incorrecta3": "routerband",
        "incorrecta4": "htpband",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    }
  
]